Toggle navigation [US Banks Directory](http://usbanksdirectory.com/)

*  Search

Privacy Policy
==============

The privacy of our visitors to **UsBanksDirectory.com** is important to us. At **UsBanksDirectory.com**, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit **UsBanksDirectory.com**, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.  

#### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.  

#### Cookies

* Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.
* Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
* Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

**UsBanksDirectory.com** reserves the right to update this privacy policy with or without notice.

Disclaimer: Please confirm this information with your bank before initiating any transaction. We are not liable for any errors or omissions in our information.  
Data used on this website is sourced from [fededirectory.frb.org](http://www.fededirectory.frb.org/) and [fdic.gov](http://fdic.gov/).

2015 © USBanksDirectory.com
